<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="9304D2FE-7C3F-4AC7-A8F8-6E577A43B093">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20121218" date="2012-12-18 21:49:10 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Memoirs</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>WP 3</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>10/18/11</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>This is the first entry I am writing directly on iWeb. We&#x2019;ll see if that effects how my thoughts flow. Noticed that my speed is a bit slower with pen and paper, and the medium also encourages bullet points, drawings, etc. that I probably wouldn&#x2019;t do when typing. Also funny to note, since transcribing my notebook entries to the computer I consistently misspelled &#x201C;entrepeneur&#x201D;. Maybe if I&#x2019;m successful one day that&#x2019;ll be funny... but probably not now that I&#x2019;ve explained it. Oh, also disregard that first entry talking about incredible sex with Taara. While it&#x2019;s not false, it presents the situation as if that&#x2019;s my only motive, or my central one when it certainly is not. Anyway, back to the mundane of what happened after recording my dream on the bus. I ran into David mantell, haven&#x2019;t seen the guy in ages, he looks a bit more mature. We exchanged small talk about what we were doing and was happy to hear he&#x2019;s working for a non-profit start-up called &#x201C;teach with africa&#x201D; working in South Africa. I told him how I wanted to be an entrepreneur (holy shit spelled it right) and he mentioned how he always wanted to work for a non-profit. He didn&#x2019;t say it explicitly but it sort of implies a rivalry, though I believe good work can be done with both models. Steve Jobs embraced the &#x201C;greed in good&#x201D; credo, realizing that technology could change peoples&#x2019; lives for the better way more than any impact a non-profit could have. Anyway, he seemed interesting and I mentioned that I had trouble connecting with my brother because he seems to still be in that college party mindset, and I&#x2019;m past it. I was impressed enough that I looked him up on facebook as he got off the bus, to see if I might reconnect. Looking through his profile I was unimpressed. Likes shows that everyone does, is into baseball, all his profile pictures are of him partying. I&#x2019;m a stickler for quality for who I let into my life and he didn&#x2019;t meet the Friend Request Bar. Oh well. Typically I enjoy people on the bus, but I found myself getting angry and hating on one loud stupid girl in particular. I think I have very strong feelings towards people one way or the other, or apathy, which is also negative. Very slightly chubby, tattoo on the lower back, talking about getting high, etc. She wasn&#x2019;t a full hipster/liberal/hippie/scenester/whatever you want to label those people. I can&#x2019;t stand these half-hearted hipster types. She made me want to continue to stop smoking weed. And the crazy thing is she was smiling the whole time, you think that would give off a positive aura, but it made me so annoyed. Surveyed the people around me wasn&#x2019;t any better as most people... as usual... were doing useless things on their iPhone. Even though I think it&#x2019;s incredible technology, I almost still want to rebel. Maybe I&#x2019;ll go to android when everyone is obsessing about the 4S, that would be the post-hipster move. Maybe I&#x2019;ll go back to a feature phone... you don&#x2019;t see people doing that (not that that&#x2019;s why I would do it). I just don&#x2019;t like this culture, and I&#x2019;m still searching for people that I can mesh with. They are few and far between, but they&#x2019;re out there. I&#x2019;d rather be alone than with a lot of people, and I&#x2019;m ok with that. Cynicism seems to be a switch that gets flipped on, or maybe it&#x2019;s on particularly strongly when I&#x2019;m on and my brain is functioning, which it certainly is today thanks to detox, thea-9, theaurapeutic omega 3 dose, centrum, and caffeine. I like my brain in this state... DONT SMOKE WEED BEN. LISTEN, I KNOW YOU WANT TO: DONT. ok superego maybe... but you remember what we decided about morals: they limit your free will. Hey, isn&#x2019;t giving in to your urges the lowest state of operation? talk about determinism!! ok ok, so there is no free will either way, and like I said, I&#x2019;m ok with that.</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
