<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="9304D2FE-7C3F-4AC7-A8F8-6E577A43B093">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20121218" date="2012-12-18 21:49:06 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Memoirs</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>WP 1</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>10/8/11</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Now we&#x2019;re not fucking around. This is a word processor as it should be. Plain. Simple. and fucking clean as all get out. Alright, I&#x2019;m sorry. That profanity was completely unnecessary. It seems my writing still has a slight latency even with this format, I suppose I will get faster as time goes on. I kind of like the idea of typing in the dark. I like the idea of not having any level of self-consciousness when it comes to what I&#x2019;m putting on the page. Anything that gets in the way of thoughts is not beneficial. Ok, what is worthy of discussing, didn&#x2019;t I have some thoughts about learning, nah that&#x2019;s all crap. Maybe this stream of consciousness writing is really the only true form of expression that exists. Writers are otherwise constantly editorializing their words as they try to create something in the name of &#x201C;meaning&#x201D; or &#x201C;profundity&#x201D;. Maybe it&#x2019;s all just a bunch of bullshit... I have become endlessly fascinated by people, especially beautiful women. I think there is something there... that allure... that is indescribable maybe its all false, maybe it&#x2019;s all hormones, but I want to believe that there is a beauty to a soulful individual that can&#x2019;t rightly be expressed in any simple form. Maybe this is how Scott got to the way he is... I have found that writing and consciousness vomit leads to a more directed train of thought. By forcing yourself to place your thoughts into coherent sentences it moves your thoughts in a more directly manner, lubricating them from idea to idea. Just looked into a macbook air, what is the goal that I&#x2019;m trying to achieve, really? To have a compact word processor?&#xD;&#xD;I don&#x2019;t really understand what the implications are of my decisions. It&#x2019;s weird how assumptions creep into your outlook on life. When I see someone dressed in a certain way, using a certain product, I create all sorts of assumptions about who they are as people. Later, when I find my assumptions to be false, I rework my models in new ways. I suppose the only way to know the intentionality of a person is to ask them, if you believe the person is even fully aware of their own intentions, or if you believe that that person is aware of their own intentions. Look at that. Just unintentionally repeated myself, I think it works to serve my point. These working models are what allow us to move forward with some causality, otherwise we are just chickens running around with our heads cut off. I like that metaphor because it is rather vivid and it evokes imagery that can be compared to people who spend so much time trying to get something done, they never have an opportunity to question what they are doing to begin with.&#xD;&#xD;My dad once told me joke relating to a lumberjack. The lumberjack is overworked and cannot cut down his trees fast enough. He spends all day cutting and can barely make his quota. Someone comes along and suggests that he sharpen his axe to which he replies &#x201C;I don&#x2019;t have time for that! I have more trees that need cutting&#x201D; I think this speaks to the way in which we can get caught in a narrow way of thinking without ever considering if our axe needs sharpening, or better yet, are we cutting the right trees, or better yet, is there another tool that could cut the trees more efficiently, or better yet could we use another material other than wood to accomplish the needs that wood is filling, or better yet can we find an alternative to the need so that the need is no longer necessary, or better yet can be eliminate or find an alternative to the objective the need is fulfilling, or better yet can we create a now objective, and eliminate the old one, creating an entirely new ecosystem and set of &#x201C;needs&#x201D;. I believe all this must be considered before swinging the axe.&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
