<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>My mind</title>
    <link>file://localhost/Users/bpgrandy/Dropbox/Public/loading/Memoirs/Memoirs.html</link>
    <description>Unleashed.&lt;br/&gt;Unedited.&lt;br/&gt;Unfiltered.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Raw.</description>
    <generator>iWeb 2.0.4</generator>
    <item>
      <title>WP 4</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/bpgrandy/Dropbox/Public/loading/Memoirs/Entries/2011/10/30_WP_4.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77451db1-41a8-4e22-9ba6-547f77ad0502</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 12:17:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Destination: hawaii. incorporated in 1962 this once mystical island that valued things contrary to the american capitalist structure: relaxation, moving slowly, appreciating nature, and enjoying the simpler ways of life has since completely lost its direction. The island (Maui) which is small enough that you would never need an automobile is peppered with them, and like every good state in the USA has become the definitive mode of transportation, despite the fact that it takes roughly 30 mins to reach one side of the island to the other.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We arrive and we immediately get a rental car, which there are 5 or 6 different companies competing for your business. Youre handed brochures which espouse all the various tours and cruises on which you can save 20%.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I read up on the history of hawaii and learned they have lost the most endemic specie of any state, and were obviously once a very independent ecosystem.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is this strange sort of juxtaposition that goes on in Maui, where if you put horse blinders on and blocked out anything outside the street, you could be in any other state in the country. But then, just outside the beautiful paved roads is a sort of third world state of development, and the ridiculous mountain scape in the background. Driving through hawaii, strip malls adourned with blockbuster, radioshack, safeway and yes even an L &amp;amp; L hawaiian BBQ outlet, which make you wonder are you really in hawaii or is this simply a sort of disneyland version of itself. Then theres costco. What once was the bustling center of commerce and marketplace in maui has become the one stop shop for the locals and tourists alike.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The parking lot was so full it was several hundred cars, it was clear that about half of the current occupants in maui were in costco.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you are placed inside this costco you have no idea that youre in hawaii, you could be in any state in the USA, but what distinguishes it is in the choice of products. Not only can you buy the standard $4,000 massage chair, foosball table, or 70” flat screen TV, local hawaiian items are sprinkled throughout the store. What was once, I am sure, an independent marketplace where hawaii goods were presented in a unique fashion has turned into the only reality that hawaii must face if it wishes to remain viable as a functioning state in the US economy. Hand made, custom cultural hawaiian icons are stacks up tall in piles immediately adjacently to peanuts in 5 lb minimum quantities or Qc10, the latest in proven body enhancement drink. My parents were constantly trying to find the cheapest price and using nothing other than that as a metric for determining quality. This is the logical eventuality of capitalism. On one hand people are driven to commoditize everything and are disconnected from the romance of the marketplace and  and places lose a sense of uniqueness. On the other hand, it is the most efficient system so more people have access to more, cheaper, which theoretically should bring more joy, health, and happiness.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Is this the inevitability that every capitalist based society faces? Sure, the US is a figure head because it is among the most developed of countries and has parading the free market the strongest, but surely if this is what the market does are not all economies eventually headed in this direction?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We ended up buying much more than we needed in costco, and then headed to safeway for a similar experience. San Francisco’s efforts to keep big box stores out have resulted in an experience, I have now realized, that is more exotic than Hawaii.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We found a “craft fair”, which was basically a group of different locals all selling the same souvenir crap. when i pressured the man with the souvenir stand admitted that he buys from a corporate dealership and I realized that everything he made is essentially built in china.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Souvenirs designed so that people can take them back to their homes and relay the message that they were lucky enough to enjoy this “exotic” vacation to hawaii. To cover themselves in what has become the mass-marketed image of what hawaii style is: Kona shells, bracelets, ukeleles, hibiscus flowers.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;purchasing milk at safeway I make a comment that the milk is $5/ gallon, implying that its cost is related to the carbon involved to get the milk fresh, and it is obviously not local. My Dad replies oh “Nov 10, Nov 5, well get the November 10, it’s almost a week fresher!” completely ignoring my comment on the expense of it. Later we realize that the milk has a pinhole leak in it, not enough to be dripping, but the side is slightly moist. I say, “Do you want to switch it out? you know they’ll have to throw it out...” My mother replies, “Yeah, I don’t want that, it’s dripping”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;When checking out at both costco and safeway I noticed native hawaii’s forced into the capitalist role of grocery store checker. They did not seem joyful in the role, just the general attitutude of complacency that so many passive of the american “workforce” have adopted. They had become part of the system just as the native americans could not resist the american capitalist force.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;When bringing out the bags of groceries that we had purchased from safeway because the quantities were too great at costco, which were also excessive, the corona handle broke smashed into the parking lot. Who is to place the liability on the broken handles?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;is it me for trying to think I could carry more than I could?&lt;br/&gt;is it the poorly tried native hawaiian for not knowing in independently bottle 6-packs?&lt;br/&gt;is it corona for designed such a poor case so that the handle broke under simply its own weight?&lt;br/&gt;is it the american mindset of wanting to constantly booze up and have accessible forms of liquor?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;we come into the condo, which was rented by a family friend, im amazed at how beautiful the cabinet work is, how nice the furniture, the spacious balcony. My mother’s response “It’s small, but it’ll do.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;there is something artificial around spaces that are “designed” for tourists that I can’t quite escape. the grass outside our timeshare is meticulously mowed, and everything seems to be so planned out its sickening.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“ok, beer time.” my mother states, exhausted after all the shopping “I think I’m going to have to go get another six”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WP 3</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/bpgrandy/Dropbox/Public/loading/Memoirs/Entries/2011/10/18_WP_3.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">668a7ebe-5669-4054-bbfe-6ccdc2e4b7e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 21:40:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>This is the first entry I am writing directly on iWeb. We’ll see if that effects how my thoughts flow. Noticed that my speed is a bit slower with pen and paper, and the medium also encourages bullet points, drawings, etc. that I probably wouldn’t do when typing. Also funny to note, since transcribing my notebook entries to the computer I consistently misspelled “entrepeneur”. Maybe if I’m successful one day that’ll be funny... but probably not now that I’ve explained it. Oh, also disregard that first entry talking about incredible sex with Taara. While it’s not false, it presents the situation as if that’s my only motive, or my central one when it certainly is not. Anyway, back to the mundane of what happened after recording my dream on the bus. I ran into David mantell, haven’t seen the guy in ages, he looks a bit more mature. We exchanged small talk about what we were doing and was happy to hear he’s working for a non-profit start-up called “teach with africa” working in South Africa. I told him how I wanted to be an entrepreneur (holy shit spelled it right) and he mentioned how he always wanted to work for a non-profit. He didn’t say it explicitly but it sort of implies a rivalry, though I believe good work can be done with both models. Steve Jobs embraced the “greed in good” credo, realizing that technology could change peoples’ lives for the better way more than any impact a non-profit could have. Anyway, he seemed interesting and I mentioned that I had trouble connecting with my brother because he seems to still be in that college party mindset, and I’m past it. I was impressed enough that I looked him up on facebook as he got off the bus, to see if I might reconnect. Looking through his profile I was unimpressed. Likes shows that everyone does, is into baseball, all his profile pictures are of him partying. I’m a stickler for quality for who I let into my life and he didn’t meet the Friend Request Bar. Oh well. Typically I enjoy people on the bus, but I found myself getting angry and hating on one loud stupid girl in particular. I think I have very strong feelings towards people one way or the other, or apathy, which is also negative. Very slightly chubby, tattoo on the lower back, talking about getting high, etc. She wasn’t a full hipster/liberal/hippie/scenester/whatever you want to label those people. I can’t stand these half-hearted hipster types. She made me want to continue to stop smoking weed. And the crazy thing is she was smiling the whole time, you think that would give off a positive aura, but it made me so annoyed. Surveyed the people around me wasn’t any better as most people... as usual... were doing useless things on their iPhone. Even though I think it’s incredible technology, I almost still want to rebel. Maybe I’ll go to android when everyone is obsessing about the 4S, that would be the post-hipster move. Maybe I’ll go back to a feature phone... you don’t see people doing that (not that that’s why I would do it). I just don’t like this culture, and I’m still searching for people that I can mesh with. They are few and far between, but they’re out there. I’d rather be alone than with a lot of people, and I’m ok with that. Cynicism seems to be a switch that gets flipped on, or maybe it’s on particularly strongly when I’m on and my brain is functioning, which it certainly is today thanks to detox, thea-9, theaurapeutic omega 3 dose, centrum, and caffeine. I like my brain in this state... DONT SMOKE WEED BEN. LISTEN, I KNOW YOU WANT TO: DONT. ok superego maybe... but you remember what we decided about morals: they limit your free will. Hey, isn’t giving in to your urges the lowest state of operation? talk about determinism!! ok ok, so there is no free will either way, and like I said, I’m ok with that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N 3</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/bpgrandy/Dropbox/Public/loading/Memoirs/Entries/2011/10/18_N_3.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e81f18e-0aa1-40c0-8487-5078ba0271c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 21:08:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>I took a nap in the middle of the day. I couldn’t shower because I was waiting on a call. It put me in this weird limbo state of decision making. Two creatures were walking side by side, one was a dog, another was similar but they were both walking on 4 legs. They were discussing something meaningful in a high level of english when they spotted me.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[drawing on two animals with an arrow that indicates gradient spotlight]&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;    We made eye contact  and they stopped talking and snarled, as if in a reactionary manner. The snarl startled me and I found myself fully awake on my couch. I haven’t fully dismissed the idea of an alternate reality that is the dream world. These two creatures/ souls chose to embody an animal form for whatever reason. It was clear to them that I didn’t belong and they exited me from their world with a quick snarl.         .            .        almost habitual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WP 2</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/bpgrandy/Dropbox/Public/loading/Memoirs/Entries/2011/10/12_Reflections_on_the_lake.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">caf37481-73e1-483f-b8a8-ca8d061e7b48</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 01:15:06 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>New Entry: This is one of those ones that serves to get the lubrication flowing in the cerebellum. Also, to reflect on my actions from a higher level and ponder some of the things I should be pondering. Why do I go on reddit for hours? I am looking, I am searching for truth. When you don’t find truth, you need a new strategy, a new approach, how new? hard to say. a different sub-reddit maybe, a different website could be, a different form of media consumption maybe, or simply an active vs. passive switch. This is the problem I have, and I assume I’m not the only one. Reading endless amounts of news, stories, and whatever the hell other people are talking about almost makes me feel like I’m moving towards having an authority on some subject. The only problem is, it’s truly endless. You will spend so much time browsing, you will never have any form of creation to show for it. This is the demise of modern era. One must be really selective and self-conscious with one’s actions, time is the most precious thing we have. It’s easy to forget that when it seems so abundant, so endless on a daily basis. Smoking weed prevents me from being able to look at my actions from a level of higher order. It traps me in those low levels of behavior, and I accept that. Perhaps me simply accepting that is a surrender to that condition. Surely, that condition can be fought against but not without a good deal of struggle. Surrendering to that alternate reality I admit is a low-character move, and yet I continuing try to justify it. Why is it that I need to escape to some alternate reality? It must be there is something lacking with the true reality. Why did I really want to smoke? All these drugs are distractions, and I post-rationalize one with another.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Creating seems to give meaning to the banal. Whether it’s designing, drawing, writing, coding, or whatever it seems to legitimize my existence. It’s creating a legacy, even if that legacy is nothing more than what’s been said. Even if that legacy drowns in the sea of voices, there are plenty of other’s that have creating things without so much the intention of originality. If I open anyone’s mind in some way or give someone even the slightest of a differentiation in perspective, I think my life to be well lived. Must we constantly alternate between these realities of feelings of ground-breaking and routine? Is there a way to maintain the high creation of something beautiful brings? It is rather self-serving, this yearning to leave a legacy. I am more interested in creating something for myself than I am trying to get meaning from others. Oh well, whatever maintains your sanity, right? and this certainly does. I don’t think I could ever talk to a friend this openly, and have them judge me as I judge myself, working through my thoughts. In a conversation it is typically expected that you have established yourself on one side or another, a constant dialogue with yourself is not encouraged. How unfortunate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N 2</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/bpgrandy/Dropbox/Public/loading/Memoirs/Entries/2011/10/9_N_2.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a5b314d-8e6d-4358-9f25-ac8f41c8895b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 9 Oct 2011 21:08:55 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>Poetry competition @ Catholic Christian? Homeschool, children 5-14, Taara is the accuracy judge, along with three of her colleagues from the Santa Clara review. “Parking behind Shrine” sign on the way here. comical “let’s find the right shrine to park next to”&lt;br/&gt;    American suburbanism in a single message&lt;br/&gt;        -Relgion Petroleum + Park&lt;br/&gt;They just recited all this Christian psycho-babble&lt;br/&gt;cults: they cray cray.&lt;br/&gt;    Hmm Louis Carroll, interesting choice for Christians.&lt;br/&gt;“Sit back &amp;amp; enjoy this ... exxxxxcittttiiiinnnggggg Reeccccciittttinnng!”&lt;br/&gt;She’s so proud of herself.&lt;br/&gt;Everyone is forced to memorize the poem, must be a Christian thing, all about reciting, brainwashing. They are more focused on not messing up than the actual meaning behind the words.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
